Kowalczyk, Judith Sullivan Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications 6312 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Judith Sullivan Kowalczyk Collection of Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Publications
1948-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kowalczyk, Judith Sullivan
Sullivan, Charles H.
Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen (BRT)
6312 PUBS
0.5 cubic feet
0.5 linear ft.
Publications.
7477233
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 26, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Railroads -- Employees; Kowalczyk, Judith Sullivan; Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
7477233
- Directory. Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Directory of the Grand Lodge and Subordinate Lodges of the Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Author: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen
    Notes: April 1948
    Format: Publication
    Language: English.
- Trainman News, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trainman News, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.3:no.37 (1949:Sep. 12). Includes article and photograph featuring Jacob Potofsky, president of ACWA.
- Elmira Association of Commerce. 44th Annual Meeting, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: 44th Annual Meeting of the Elmira Association of Commerce Honoring the Centennial of the Erie Railroad's Arrival in Elmira on October 2, 1849, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Elmira Association of Commerce
- Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen 29th Convention, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: En route to Twenty-Ninth Convention Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1950; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Miami Florida. September 1950
  - Item 2: En route to Twenty-Ninth Convention Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Miami Florida. September 1950. Copy 2.
  - Item 3: En route to Twenty-Ninth Convention Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: Miami Florida. September 1950. Copy 3.
- New York State Association Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen & Ladies Auxiliary. 23rd Annual Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 23rd Annual Convention, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: New York State Association Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen and Ladies Auxiliary
    Notes: Manger Hotel, Rochester, NY, July 31, August 1-2, 1959
- Letter W. P. Kennedy to William Abbott, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Letter: W. P. Kennedy to William Abbott, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: William P. Kennedy
    Notes: May 10, 1962
- New York State Association Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen & Ladies Auxiliary. 32nd Annual Convention, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: 32nd Annual Convention, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Notes: DeWitt Clinton Hotel, Albany, NY, August 15-17, 1968.